auctionexport.com 2016-06-01

# Privacy Policy - Auction Export

| 

|  |    
---|---|---  
  
  | 

###  PRIVACY POLICY

AuctionExport.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of our website. We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users' right to privacy. By using www.auctionexport.com , please carefully read that you are agreeing to all the terms and conditions of our privacy policy. 

**Collection of Information**   
Our website AuctionExport.com will request that you provide personal information, such as a residential address, an email address and a phone number information when you registering to create an account with us. Auction Export collects information about users during registration, vehicle purchasing and rarely anywhere else. Our policy is to only collect personal information that you knowingly and specifically provide to us. As you browse the site, Auction Export collects information about your visit, not about you personally. Via web server logs and browser cookie files, we monitor statistics such as: 

  * How many people visit our site
  * Which pages people visit on our site
  * From which domains our visitors come (e.g., google.com, yahoo.com, bing.com, aol.com etc.)
  * Which browsers people use to visit our site (Internet Explorer, FireFox, Opera, Chrome, Safari)

While we gather this information, none of it is associated with you as an individual. We use these statistics to improve our website, to monitor its performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use.  
**  
Use of Information **   
Auction Export uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and does not disclose this information to third parties unless you first provide us with your express consent. Information obtained via our website is strictly used by Auction Export internally. Any information collected during the registration process will not be distributed or sold to outside parties unless we are ordered to do so by a legal process, such as a court order.  

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a small file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from Auction Export to the hard drive of your computer, enabling us to recognize you as a unique user and increase the efficiency of your exploration of our website. Through our cookies we receive such anonymous information as your internet service provider, your computer's browser, and some of your online surfing trends and patterns. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you will find them used on most major web sites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, however, if you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you have received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that while Auction Export does not require you to use cookies, certain functions may not work properly if you set your browser to not accept cookies. 

Please be aware that we will not disclose any information obtained through our cookies unless legally bound to do so. 

**Security**   
To protect the transactions conducted on our website, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the data you input into our website. 

Auction Export places great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with our users. To protect the transactions conducted on our website, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the data you input into our website. 

We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized personnel have access to user information. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of information will not occur, we use all reasonable efforts to prevent this. You should bear in mind that transmission of information over the internet is never entirely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of information you transmit to the site and any such transmission is at your own risk. 

It is advisable to close your browser when you have finished your user session to help ensure others do not access your personal information if you use a shared computer or a computer in a public place. 

We have security features to safeguard all personal and anonymous information from unauthorized access. To protect the transactions conducted on our website, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the data you input into our website. 

**Email Addresses**   
If you provide us your email address, we may email you about our website or our services. From time to time, we will also send you emails that may include information, special sale promotions and other offers that may be of interest to you. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**   
We reserve the right to update our privacy policy at any time. We will post a notification on our home page, If we make changes to this version of our privacy policy. Your continued use of our website following the posting of the notification will constitute your agreement with all of the terms and conditions of our new privacy policy. 

**General**   
Auction Export is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Third-Party Websites to which it may provide links. Those are links to websites maintained by other businesses and organizations. Those links are provided as a service to users. AuctionExport.com also cannot take any liability for the accuracy or source of the information contained on any of those websites or the content of any file the user might download from those sites. We recommend to review the privacy policies of these websites to be informed of their respective privacy practices. 

If you have any concerns or questions about our privacy policy or the manner in which we are implementing it, please contact us at [info@auctionexport.com](mailto:info@auctionexport.com)

|
